<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Brian Anders on More than Men</title>
    <link>https://morethanmen.org/author/brian-anders/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Brian Anders on More than Men</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2014 11:00:34 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://morethanmen.org/author/brian-anders/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Who could ask for anything more?</title>
      <link>https://morethanmen.org/posts/01842_who-could-ask-for-anything-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2014 11:00:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://morethanmen.org/posts/01842_who-could-ask-for-anything-more/</guid>
      <description>This weekend is a special weekend for me. On Saturday, I will celebrate 11 years of marriage with my brilliant, amazing, strong and determined wife, Elyse. And on Sunday, we will celebrate Elyse’s birthday, and Father’s Day.
This weekend, in many ways, is a celebration of my life. The beauty of this weekend is I can share it with those I love most. And while the commercial world says I need to go out and buy something made of steel for our anniversary, and buy some trinket or some other gift for Elyse’s birthday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WTF Hollywood?!?! You&#39;re better than that</title>
      <link>https://morethanmen.org/posts/01833_wtf-hollywood-youre-better-than-that/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2014 11:00:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://morethanmen.org/posts/01833_wtf-hollywood-youre-better-than-that/</guid>
      <description>What do the following 6 movies have in common?
Group 1
 Kick-Ass 2 Man of Steel Sharknado We’re the Millers The Wolverine World War Z  What do the following 6 movies have in common?
Group 2
 21 Jump Street The Amazing Spider-Man 2 The Avengers Rush Star Trek Into the Darkness This is the End  Both groups have been judged using a system called The Bechdel Test.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feminist Princesses? FUCK YEAH!</title>
      <link>https://morethanmen.org/posts/01817_feminist-princesses-fuck-yeah/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Apr 2014 11:00:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://morethanmen.org/posts/01817_feminist-princesses-fuck-yeah/</guid>
      <description>Being between jobs, I spend a lot of time trying to keep myself busy during the day. I tend to do a lot of chores and small projects that have gone neglected. Over the last 2 months, the small projects have led several afternoon shopping runs. During my shopping runs, I tend to swing through the toy section and see about something small for the kids.
When I was a kid, Barbie dominated the toy section.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
