<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tesla&#39;s Butler on More than Men</title>
    <link>https://chaos46692.github.io/author/teslas-butler/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tesla&#39;s Butler on More than Men</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 May 2012 09:13:34 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chaos46692.github.io/author/teslas-butler/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Compassionate Skepticism</title>
      <link>https://chaos46692.github.io/posts/00911_compassionate-skepticism/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2012 09:13:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chaos46692.github.io/posts/00911_compassionate-skepticism/</guid>
      <description>I’m gonna let you guys in on a little secret today: science isn’t cheap. There’s a lot of fundraising that goes on to support the research which leads to the treatments that make life on planet earth longer and better. Unfortunately not everything gets the financial backing that it deserves.
What causes do and don&amp;rsquo;t get funded? Well, it isn&amp;rsquo;t always as impartial as you&amp;rsquo;d hope. Helping men past their prime get it up obviously isn&amp;rsquo;t a very pressing concern, but the prevalence of 80 year olds with limp dicks and disposable income prompted the creation of Viagra over treatments for say&amp;hellip; for Sickle Cell Anemia, which is actually life threatening (unlike erectile dysfunction) but tends to effect minority populations disproportionately.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Simple Steps to a More Inclusive Skeptical Community</title>
      <link>https://chaos46692.github.io/posts/00881_3-simple-steps-to-a-more-inclusive-skeptical-community/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Apr 2012 09:06:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chaos46692.github.io/posts/00881_3-simple-steps-to-a-more-inclusive-skeptical-community/</guid>
      <description>###1) Make Skeptical Events Across the Country Less Alcohol Centric
Imagine you&amp;rsquo;re a 20 year old who is passionately invested in skepticism. You really want to meet others who feel the same way you do and have enlightening conversations with them! You go online and do a quick look-up of skeptical events held in your area. &amp;ldquo;Oh hey, Skeptics in the Pub!&amp;rdquo; you exclaim to yourself. Then it hits you: in the pub&amp;hellip; You&amp;rsquo;re not 21.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
