<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Carl on More than Men</title>
    <link>https://morethanmen.org/author/carl/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Carl on More than Men</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2013 11:38:44 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://morethanmen.org/author/carl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Facebook doesn&#39;t care if you die</title>
      <link>https://morethanmen.org/posts/01775_facebook-doesnt-care-if-you-die/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2013 11:38:44 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://morethanmen.org/posts/01775_facebook-doesnt-care-if-you-die/</guid>
      <description>Dear Mr Zuckerberg,
It must be pretty awesome to be a white dude with billions of dollars. It must be nice to be able to afford peace of mind. You do realize that not everyone is a billionaire right? Because when Facebook makes decisions to allow any timeline to be found by name alone that&amp;rsquo;s seriously messed up. Your suggestions to make things more secure are laughable:
   Share each post with the people you want to be able to see it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I have learned from the women in my life</title>
      <link>https://morethanmen.org/posts/01610_what-i-have-learned-from-the-women-in-my-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2013 09:27:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://morethanmen.org/posts/01610_what-i-have-learned-from-the-women-in-my-life/</guid>
      <description>To put it in skeptic terms, #ShutUpAndListen means &amp;ldquo;You lack evidence relevant to this problem, so learn from those who have it.&amp;quot;
So first off let&amp;rsquo;s address the elephant in the room. I simply cannot add anything to discussion of Ron Lindsay&amp;rsquo;s opening remarks that holds a candle to what&amp;rsquo;s been said by Secular Women, Dan Fincke, Adam Lee and a whole host of other people. I&amp;rsquo;m not even going to try because the more I think about it the more irritated I become about Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stay-at-home dude</title>
      <link>https://morethanmen.org/posts/01558_stay-at-home-dude/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Feb 2013 09:00:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://morethanmen.org/posts/01558_stay-at-home-dude/</guid>
      <description>A friend posted a link to this article on Slate about a married man with no kids who is a homemaker. I loved the article. Due, in no small part, to the fact that this very well could have been how my life ended up. At one point in my life I was a physics major dating a chemical engineer - pretty clear who was going to be earning the big bucks there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Respect as it applies to anti-harassment policies</title>
      <link>https://morethanmen.org/posts/01030_respect-as-it-applies-to-anti-harassment-policies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2012 09:00:01 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://morethanmen.org/posts/01030_respect-as-it-applies-to-anti-harassment-policies/</guid>
      <description>As an organizer for my local Skeptic group, it was important to me to include an anti-harassment policy. My co-organizer and I very much wanted the gender ratio to be as close to 50/50 as it could be, for both speakers and attendees. To that end I wanted a good anti-harassment policy in place. I never imagined that it would be an issue. I guess at heart I&amp;rsquo;ve been far too much of an optimist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contribute</title>
      <link>https://morethanmen.org/posts/contribute/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://morethanmen.org/posts/contribute/</guid>
      <description>Howdy There&amp;rsquo;s nothing to see here. MtM has been shelved for quite a while and I&amp;rsquo;m not putting any effort into it, but I may allow limited contributions in the future</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
