<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Anthroslug on More than Men</title>
    <link>https://chaos46692.github.io/author/anthroslug/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Anthroslug on More than Men</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 May 2012 09:15:14 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chaos46692.github.io/author/anthroslug/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Gender, Sex, and Where They Dont Meet</title>
      <link>https://chaos46692.github.io/posts/00954_gender-sex-and-where-they-dont-meet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2012 09:15:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chaos46692.github.io/posts/00954_gender-sex-and-where-they-dont-meet/</guid>
      <description>[This article was first published on November 23, 2011]
My partner, Kaylia, has many friends who are part of the transgender community. These are people who don’t fit the traditional gender roles in that they are living as members of the opposite sex, are undergoing medical procedures to change sex, don’t find themselves fitting into either male or female sex roles, or are biologically not clearly male or female to begin with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conscience Meets Reality, or How I Learned to Stop Worrying About Other People&#39;s Sex Lives</title>
      <link>https://chaos46692.github.io/posts/00886_conscience-meets-reality-or-how-i-learned-to-stop-worrying-about-other-peoples-sex-lives/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 May 2012 10:30:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chaos46692.github.io/posts/00886_conscience-meets-reality-or-how-i-learned-to-stop-worrying-about-other-peoples-sex-lives/</guid>
      <description>[This article was originally posted on March 16, 2012]
So, the Blunt Amendment (full text here) was voted down two weeks ago. The Blunt Amendment, for those not in the know, would have altered the requirements placed on employers that provide health insurance to their employees so that they would not be required to have insurance coverage that provided services that the employer or the insurance company finds morally objectionable. As spelled out in the amendment itself:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Friend Zone...Like the Twilight Zone, but Less Real</title>
      <link>https://chaos46692.github.io/posts/00867_the-friend-zonelike-the-twilight-zone-but-less-real/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2012 09:47:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chaos46692.github.io/posts/00867_the-friend-zonelike-the-twilight-zone-but-less-real/</guid>
      <description>[This originally appeared on Anthroslug&amp;rsquo;s personal blog on April 2, 2012.]
I loathe the term “the Friend Zone.” It is one of those terms that seems to get thrown around without much thought, generally by men as an excuse for why they have had little success with dating and/or sex. My dislike for this term comes from my often-stated dislike for sloppy thinking and irrational claims, and as such I am not going to get into a discussion of whether or not the idea of the Friend Zone is born out of issues pertaining to privilege or misogyny (besides, [more articulate individuals than myself have already done so]](https://chaos46692.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
